Everybody loves the idea of authentic people until they see what that authenticity looks like in practice and up close.
I've always noticed that some of the most real, down-to-earth, independent thinkers who are so true to themselves are disliked by people in their day-to-day lives.
Everybody loves true, authentic people from afar, but whenever they become close with them, they can't handle it.
Y'all do not actually want to be friends with a real-ass bitch.
You want to be friends with group thinkers.
You want to be friends with yes-men.
You want to be friends with other people who are insecure.
I actually want to be friends with people who share the same insecurities with you.
People who share the same coping mechanisms with you.
People who don't force you to look in the mirror and see who you really are so you can stay in your state of delusion.
People who do not threaten your reality.
Y'all love to repost the real-ass bitches videos on TikTok.
The think pieces that sound good.
Ideas that come from being someone who's been through shit and thinks for themselves,
but then you get around the person and you can't handle it because they bring out all of your insecurities.
They trigger something so deep inside of you, they show you what you're not.
You start projecting on them.
You can't handle them.
You ostracize them.
Because deep down inside, you actually don't want to be friends with a real-ass bitch.
I promise you, you don't.
True, real, independent thinkers typically only get along with other people who are like that.
Other people who are super confident.
Other people who know themselves really well.
But when you pair them with the average person, the average thinker, the group think, the friend group, it doesn't work.
Most really, really real ones don't even do friend groups.
Me included.